<resources>
    <string name="app_name">MusicDraft</string>
    <string name="hello">Hey there, </string>
    <string name="create_account">Create an Account</string>
    <string name="welcome">Welcome Back</string>
    <string name="nickname">Nickname</string>
    <string name="email">Email</string>
    <string name="password">Password</string>
    <string name="hide_password">Hide password</string>
    <string name="show_password">show_password</string>
    <string name="terms_and_conditions">By continuing you accept our Privacy Policy and Term of Use</string>
    <string name="terms_and_conditions_header">Privacy Policy and Terms of Use</string>
    <string name="terms_and_conditions_body"> \n

        1. Introduction\n
        Welcome to MusicDraft! By using our app, you agree to comply with and be bound by the following terms and conditions.
        Please review them carefully.\n\n

        2. Data Collection\n
        We collect personal data to improve our services. This includes your name, email address, and usage data.
        We are committed to protecting your privacy and ensuring that your personal information is handled in a safe and responsible manner.\n\n

        3. Usage of Data\n
        Your data is used to provide and enhance our services, respond to customer inquiries, and comply with legal obligations.
        We do not sell or share your personal information with third parties without your consent, except as necessary to provide our services or comply with the law.\n\n

        4. User Responsibilities\n
        You agree not to misuse our services. This includes, but is not limited to, unauthorized access to our systems, distributing malware, or engaging in activities that harm other users.\n\n

        5. Modifications to Terms\n
        We may update these terms and conditions from time to time. You will be notified of any changes through our app or via email.
        Continued use of the app after such modifications constitutes your acceptance of the new terms.\n\n

        6. Contact Information\n
        If you have any questions about these terms, please contact us at support@musicdraft.com.\n\n

        By using MusicDraft, you acknowledge that you have read and understood these terms and agree to be bound by them.\n\n

        Last updated: [27/06/2024]
    </string>
    <string name="register">Register</string>
    <string name="or">or</string>
    <string name="go_to_login">Already have an account? Login</string>
    <string name="login">Login</string>
    <string name="forgot_password">Forgot your password</string>
</resources>